Guide to the John L. Hennessy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0700
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- President's records, 2002-2003; Accession ARCH-2005-173
  - Pacific Ten Conference (Pac-10)( Folder A), 09/26/2002-05/27/2003; O 3.47 (Box 7)
  - Pacific Ten Conference (Pac-10), 36313; O 3.47 (Box 7)
  - Pacific Ten Conference (Pac-10), 06/06/2003-08/27/2003; O 3.47 (Box 7)
  - Businesses, O 5 (Box 7)
  - Other Colleges and Universities (FOLDER C), 07/02/2003-06/26/2003; O 8 (Box 7)
  - Other Colleges and Universities (FOLDER B), 03/07/2003-06/06/2003; O 8 (Box 7)
  - Other Colleges and Universities (FOLDER A), 10/24/2001-02/28/2003; O 8 (Box 7)
  - Student, 10/24/2002-07/10/2003; ST 1 (Box 8)
  - Student (Groups), 10/07/2002-07/18/2003; ST 1.1 (Box 8)
  - ASSU, 09/26/2002-08/18/2003; ST 2 (Box 8)
  - Bechtel International Center, 03/05/2001-07/23/2003; ST 3.5 (Box 8)
  - ASIA-PACIFIC Scholars Program, 1999-2003; ST 7.1 (Box 8)
  - American Association of Universities, 10/07/2002-08/31/2003; O 8.7 (Box 8)
  - Duke University, 08/27/2003; O 8.12 (Box 8)
  - Harvard University, 12/05/2000-08/18/2003; O 8.23 (Box 8)
  - Univ. of CA (All Campuses), 12/09/2002-08/13/2003; O 8.43 (Box 8)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 10/04/2002-05/23/2003; O 11 (Box 8)
  - Inst. for Research on Women/Gender (same as CROW), 09/24/1999-12/03/02; R 1.8 (Box 8)
- President's records, 2003-2004; Accession ARCH-2006-057
  - Provost's Office, 1/12/2004-06/23/2004; AA 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dean of Chapel, 2/26/2001; AA 1.8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Graduate Fellowships, 04/14/2002-08/16/2004; AA 1.12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Student Issues, 08/28/2002-07/20/2004; AA 1.13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Emeriti, 09/03/2001-04/07/2003; AA 2.2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Affirmative Action, 11/26/2001-02/06/2003; AA 2.3.3 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Development, 08/07/2003-08/24/2004; AA 2.7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - University Fellows, 06/21/2002-06/10/2004; AA 2.9 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate Studies/Issues, 05/01/2002-08/12/2004; AA 3 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Accreditation Issues / Very General/ CHEA, 09/17/2003-08/02/2004; AA 3.4 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ratings / Rankings, 03/13/2003-04/27/2004; AA 3.5 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Continuing Studies/Education, 10/18/2001-04/02/2003; AA 3.6 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - TV, Cable, Ch 51, etc., 10/18/2001-06/01/2004; AA 3.9.1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Summer Session, 12/17/2001; AA 3.16 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Sophomore Seminars, 03/18/2002-09/02/2003; AA 3.18.2 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Prof. Dr. William Hurlbut, 02/25/2004-07/29/2004; AA 4.1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - School of Humanities & Sciences, 06/26/2003-08/23/2004; AA 4.1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Humanities Center, 10/08/2002-03/03/2004; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - MLK Jr. Papers project, 02/12/1997-11/10/2003; AA 4.1.1/3 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Applied Physics, Dept of, 09/05/2003-02/02/2004; AA 4.1.8 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Art, Dept of (Academic), 11/27/2002-07/29/2004; AA 4.1.9 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Chemistry, Dept of, 10/18/2002-03/26/2004; AA 4.1.13 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Computer Science, Dept of, 04/21/2003-01/07/2004; AA 4.1.17 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Drama, Dept of, 03/15/2002-02/02/2004; AA 4.1.18 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Economics, Dept of, 10/03/2003-05/01/04; AA 4.1.20 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Stanford Inst. for Economic Policy Research (SIEPR), 10/09/2002-07/01/2004; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - English, Dept of, 11/18/2003-07/06/2004; AA 4.1.21 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Gumbrecht, Hans Ulrich, 11/15/2002-05/25/2004; AA 4.1.22 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - History, Dept of, 11/22/2002-01/07/2004; AA 4.1.25 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Hopkins Marine Station, 10/29/2001-12/15/2003; AA 4.1.28 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Music, Dept of, 12/03/2002-07/23/2004; AA 4.1.29 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Athletics, Dept of, 01/08/2003-08/31/2004; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Football Games, 09/24/2001-05/04/2004; AA 4.1.30/1 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Philosophy, Dept of, 01/11/2002-04/02/2002; AA 4.1.32 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Physics, Dept of, 09/11/2001-05/10/2004; AA 4.1.33 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Political Science, Dept of, 04/11/2002-12/17/2003; AA 4.1.34 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Psychology, Dept of, 12/12/2001-07/06/2004; AA 4.1.35 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Graduate School of Business, 08/28/2003-08/26/2004; AA 4.2 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Earth Science, School of, 09/19/2002-08/27/2004; AA 4.3 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Global Climate and Energy Project, GCEP, 11/18/2002-01/06/2004; AA 4.3.1 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Engineering, School of, 09/04/2003-08/09/2004; AA 4.4 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Education, School of, 10/07/2003-07/19/2004; AA 4.5 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Hoover Institute, 03/18/2003-07/26/2004; AA 4.9 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Learning Lab, Larry/Sweden/Global Learning Institute Wallenburg, 10/28/2002-06/01/2004; AA 4.10.4 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - CISAC, 09/10/2002-04/08/2004; AA 4.10.6 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Latin American Studies, Center for, 05/22/2002-05/12/2004; AA 4.11 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Russian and East European, Center for, 11/07/2003-12/08/2003; AA 4.11.1 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Libraries, Stanford, 09/02/2003-08/02/2004; AA 4.12 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - CSLI, 03/10/2003-09/03/2003; AA 4.14.1 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - School of Law, 08/18/2002-08/24/2004; AA 4.15 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - ITSS, 09/04/2003-10/14/2003; AA 4.22 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Awards/Prizes, Misc., 08/05/2003-08/26/2004; AA 5 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 04/21/2003-05/10/2004; AA 5.2 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Gold Spike Award, 04/03/2000-04/05/2003; AA 5.26 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Grants, Scholarships, Misc., 01/05/2001-08/05/2004; AA 6 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Fellowships, Misc/General Information, 09/03/2003-07/01/2004; AA 8 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Fulbright Fellowship/Scholarship, 07/02/2004-08/24/2004; AA 8.16 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Knight Fellowships/Foundation, 09/02/2003-05/25/2004; AA 8.25 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Terman Fellowship, 3/15/2004; AA 8.30 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Tanner Lectures, 10/23/2003-06/14/2004; AA 9.19 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Endowed Chairs/Professorships, Miscellaneous, 08/01/2003-08/28/2003; AA 10 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Stanford Mansion/Stanford Misc, 09/06/2001-07/19/2004; AD 1 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Founders Day and Historical Society, 12/09/2002-03/03/2004; AD 1.2 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - ROTC, 11/08/2002-05/03/2004; AD 2.26 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Fundamental Process, 11/27/2002; AD 3.10 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - President's Office/ John Hennessy, 01/19/2002-08/23/2004; AD 4 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Workshop on Gender Equity, 02/04/2004-03/22/2004; AD 4.3 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Hoover House, Staff, Car, 09/23/1999-05/02/2003; AD 4.7 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - General Correspondence, 09/18/2003-08/30/2004; AD 4.20 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Clippings/Editorials, 05/17/1999-07/06/2004; AD 4.20.1 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Condolence Letters, 10/10/2002-08/27/2004; AD 4.20.2 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 10/01/2003-08/06/2004; AD 4.20.3 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Letters of Appreciation, 12/02/2002-08/11/2004; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Invitations (Folder 1), 09/02/2003-11/17/2003; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Invitations ( Folder 2), 11/17/2003-03/30/2004; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Invitations (Folder 3), 03/30/2004-08/31/2004; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Nonsense, 09/02/2003-08/31/2004; AD 4.20.5 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Nonsense Individuals (Seri Raniero), 09/30/2003-08/16/2004; AD 4.20.5 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Search/Recommendation, 09/30/2003-04/09/2004; AD 4.20.6 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Recommendation Letters, Students, 01/06/2003-02/20/2004; AD 4.20.6/1 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Complaint Letters, 10/15/2002-08/23/2004; AD 4.20.7 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Solicitation Letters (Folder 1), 11/17/2000-02/17/2004; AD 4.20.8 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Solicitation Letters (Folder 2), 02/18/2004-08/25/2004; AD 4.20.8 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - University Communications, 05/06/2002-06/09/2004; AD 4.22 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Campus Relations, 02/08/1999-06/22/2004; AD 6 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Admissions, 12/29/2001-08/30/2004; AD 8.1 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Student Affairs, VPUE, 09/05/2003-07/26/2004; AD 8.8 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Cowell Health Center, 6/2/2003; AD 8.9 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Stanford in Washington, 10/01/1999-11/11/2000; AD 8.10.1 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Overseas Studies, 09/30/2002-08/02/2004; AD 8.11 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Financial Aid, 10/01/2002-04/22/2004; AD 8.12 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, Housing, 11/21/2001-08/23/2004; AD 8.18 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Hanna House, 10/19/1999-09/24/2001; AD 8.18.2 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Housing/Dining Services-Students, 09/17/1998-08/27/2004; AD 8.18.11 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Registrar - Bursar, 09/16/2003-07/16/2004; AD 8.21 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Employee and Personnel Relations (Human Resources), 09/02/2003-07/12/2004; AD 10 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Stanford Labor Action Coalition, 10/07/2002-05/25/2004; AD 10 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Employment Inquiries, 09/16/2003-08/31/2004; AD 10.1 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Outdoor Art, Committee, 6/3/2004; AD 10.7.4 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - United Stanford Employees, USE, 08/31/2000-04/04/2002; AD 10.7.8 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Events, Stanford and the Public, 02/12/2001-04/04/2004; AD 11.7.5/1 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Lively Arts at Stanford, 10/08/2003-02/06/2004; AD 11.7.5/2 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Freshman Orientation, 7/23/2004; AD 11.7.7 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - External Media & Publications (Folder 1), 09/01/2002-12/30/2002; AD 11.8 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - External Media & Publications (Folder 2), 01/13/2003-08/20/2004; AD 11.8 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Stanford University Press, 09/14/2001-07/28/2004; AD 11.8.9 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Surveys, Questionnaires, 03/28/2002-08/05/2004; AD 11.8.10 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Stanford Media & Publications, 09/12/2002-06/16/2004; AD 11.8.11 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Controller's Office, 09/13/2001-02/12/2004; AD 12.2 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Admin. Resources, 11/12/2002-02/11/2004; AD 12.2/3 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Stanford Management Co., 08/07/1994-08/26/2004; AD 12.3 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - McCaffery, Michael, 05/02/2002-03/15/2004; AD 12.3.1 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Budget, Tim Warner, 09/09/1999-03/25/2002; AD 12.5 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Tuition, 07/02/2001-02/13/2003; AD 12.5.4 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Institutional Planning, 09/09/1999-03/21/2003; AD 12.6 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Risk Management, 10/31/1999-06/01/2002; AD 12.8 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Development Office, Misc., 05/04/2000-06/03/2004; AD 12.10.1 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - President's Discretionary, 11/05/1999-11/18/1999; AD 12.10.2 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Student Fund Raising/etc., 6/2/2004; AD 12.10.2/1 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - President's Fund, 07/16/2002-04/24/2003; AD 12.10.2/2 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Stanford Fund, 04/16/2002-07/20/2004; AD 12.10.2/3 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Development, Events, 12/03/2001-08/14/2003; AD 12.10.2/5 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Founders and Hoover House Circle, 09/01/2003-04/05/2004; AD 12.10.2/6 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Donor Relations, 9/1/2002; AD 12.10.2/7 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Asian Relations, General, 09/05/2001-08/31/2004; AD 12.10.2/9 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Housing/Land Issues, 01/01/1999-04/29/2004; AD 12.14.1 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Art Gallery & Museums, 01/09/2002-02/03/2004; AD 12.14.7/1 (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Stanford Bookstore, 09/08/1999-05/23/2002; AD 12.14.7/5 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Facilities Planning/University Architect, 02/01/1995-08/27/2004; AD 12.14.7/29 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - The Stanford Faculty Club, 10/13/2000-12/30/2000; AD 12.14.7/30 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Jasper Ridge, 10/17/2000-01/16/2003; AD 12.14.7/43 (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Memorial Church, 08/22/2001-08/18/2004; AD 12.14.7/50 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Parking & Transportation, 07/17/2002-07/23/2004; AD 12.14.7/53 (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - Tresidder Memorial, 4/24/2003; AD 12.14.7/64 (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - Conferences, Misc., 01/29/2002-07/23/2004; AD 13.10.1 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - University/Industry Relations, 09/23/2000-10/31/2003; AD 15 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Alumni Relations, 09/26/2002-06/01/2004; AL 1 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Stanford Parents, 10/30/2001-08/30/2004; AL 1.1/1 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Task Force on Alumni Relations, 12/03/2003-08/04/2004; AL 1.2 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Alumni Correspondence, 06/27/2002-08/31/2004; AL 1.3 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Alumni Events, 11/19/2001-10/28/2003; AL 1.7 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - SAA - 2000 (Stanford Alumni Association), 08/02/2002-08/23/2004; AL 3 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - SAA - 2000 (Stanford Alumni Association), 09/23/2003-08/23/2004; AL 3.1 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Alumni Giving (OOD), 11/5/2003; AL 5 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Academic Council, 09/24/2003-06/10/2004; C 1 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 10/19/1999-06/01/2004; C 2 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Academic Council Advisory Board, 05/13/2002-07/28/2004; C 3 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Academic Council - Steering Committee - STC, 5/17/2004; C 4.1 (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - University Committees, 10/12/2001-08/12/2004; C 6 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Committee of 15, 10/28/1999; C 6.1 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Government Relations, 09/17/2003-07/19/2004; G 1 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - California State Government, 09/19/2003-08/03/2004; G 1.2 (Box 6, Folder 152)
  - U.S. Governmental Relations, 02/20/2001-08/30/2004; G 3 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - Department of Defense (DoD), 09/22/2003-05/18/2004; G 3.7 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Department of Energy (DoE), 10/02/2002-06/14/2004; G 3.7.2 (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - National Aeronautics & Space Administration (NASA), 03/03/2004-08/30/2004; G 3.7.4 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Health & Human Services, Office of Civil Rights, 09/02/2003-02/18/2004; G 3.8.1 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - National Institutes of Health (NIH), 8/30/2004; G 3.8.2 (Box 6, Folder 158)
  - Department of Education, U.S. (USDE), 09/02/2003-12/15/2003; G 3.8.3 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Internal Revenue Services, 10/18/2002-10/22/2003; G 3.18.1 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - NSF - National Science Foundation, 10/08/2003-08/30/2004; G 3.19 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Local Government / Local Business, 10/25/2002-02/12/2004; G 4 (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Foreign Government Relations, misc., 01/16/2003-08/30/2004; G 5 (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - CA Institute for Federal Policy Research, 09/17/2003-07/16/2004; G 7 (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Stanford In Government, 11/5/1999; G 8 (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - United Nations, 09/13/1999-10/22/2003; G 12 (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Stanford Health Services/Kaiser, 2/2/2004; SHS 3 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Packard Children's Hospital, 09/16/2001-06/10/2004; SHS 7 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Medical Organizations Misc., 12/08/2000-08/02/2001; SHS 8 (Box 7, Folder 169)
  - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, 09/10/2002-05/22/2004; SHS 9 (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - Hospitals, Centers & Clinics, 05/12/2000-03/12/2004; SHS 13 (Box 7, Folder 171)
  - School of Medicine Administration, 11/06/2002-08/20/2004; M 1 (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Medical School Development, 11/28/2001-03/26/2002; M 2 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Medical School, Misc., 09/07/2001-04/21/2002; M 5 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Institute for Cancer/Stem Cell Biology & Med., 12/10/2002-05/26/2004; M 5.1 (Box 7, Folder 175)
  - Organizations, Misc. (folder 1), 09/02/2003-01/20/2004; O 1 (Box 7, Folder 176)
  - Organizations, Misc. (folder 2), 1/20/2004-03/17/2004; O 1 (Box 7, Folder 177)
  - Organizations, Misc. (folder 3), 03/17/2004-06/14/2004; O 1 (Box 7, Folder 178)
  - Organizations, Misc. (folder 4), 06/17/2004-08/30/2004; O 1 (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - Council on Competitiveness, 06/17/2003-08/10/2004; O 1.2 (Box 7, Folder 180)
  - Stanford Research Institute, 03/24/2000-05/13/2003; O 2.11 (Box 7, Folder 181)
  - Association of American Colleges and Universities (AAC&U), 05/18/2004-08/30/2004; O 3 (Box 8, Folder 182)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Ed. (COFHE), 10/08/2003-07/16/2004; O 3.1 (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - Consortium of Social Science Association, 10/15/2000-05/11/2004; O 3.3 (Box 8, Folder 184)
  - Association Pacific Rim University, 09/10/2003-08/31/2004; O 3.4 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 09/25/2003-08/03/2004; O 3.7 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - American Council on Education, 09/15/2003-06/23/2004; O 3.8 (Box 8, Folder 187)
  - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 09/04/2002-08/18/2004; O 3.10 (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - The College Board, 09/16/2002-05/30/2004; O 3.25 (Box 8, Folder 189)
  - Aspen Institute, 8/30/2000; O 3.37 (Box 8, Folder 190)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE), 10/03/2002-06/24/2004; O 3.38 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 04/29/2003-07/26/2004; O 3.43 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 07/14/2003-08/25/2004; O 3.44 (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Pacific Ten Conference (Pac-10), 01/28/2002-08/25/2004; O 3.47 (Box 8, Folder 194)
  - CA Business of Higher Education (BHEF), 6/10/2003; O 3.56 (Box 8, Folder 195)
  - Athletic Organizations, Misc, 05/14/2000-12/21/2000; O 4 (Box 8, Folder 196)
  - Korn/Ferry International, 07/05/2001-06/16/2004; O 5.1 (Box 8, Folder 197)
  - Political Groups, Misc., 07/11/2000-12/26/2001; O 6 (Box 8, Folder 198)
  - Research Organizations, 03/25/2003-08/23/2004; O 7 (Box 8, Folder 199)
  - Council of Presidents, 01/30/2002-07/16/2004; O 7.16 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Colleges and Universities (folder 1), 06/24/2003-12/16/2003; O 8 (Box 8, Folder 201)
  - Colleges and Universities (folder 2), 12/16/2003-04/06/2004; O 8 (Box 8, Folder 202)
  - Colleges and Universities (folder 3), 04/08/2004-06/21/2004; O 8 (Box 9, Folder 203)
  - Colleges and Universities (folder 4), 07/06/2004-08/27/2004; O 8 (Box 9, Folder 204)
  - American Association of Universities (AAU), 09/03/2003-08/09/2004; O 8.7 (Box 9, Folder 205)
  - Association of Independent California Colleges and Universities, 01/30/2001-05/13/2004; O 8.9 (Box 9, Folder 206)
  - Caltech, 8/13/2003; O 8.16 (Box 9, Folder 207)
  - California State Universities, 12/19/2000-06/01/2004; O 8.17 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Columbia University, 09/09/1999-06/24/2004; O 8.18 (Box 9, Folder 209)
  - Cornell University, 04/03/2000-06/01/2004; O 8.19 (Box 9, Folder 210)
  - Harvard University, 07/07/2003-03/04/2004; O 8.23 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Peking University, 09/15/1999-06/16/2004; O 8.30 (Box 9, Folder 212)
  - Princeton University, 01/25/2000-04/16/2004; O 8.36 (Box 9, Folder 213)
  - Nine (9) Provosts, 4/24/2000; O 8.39 (Box 9, Folder 214)
  - Univ. of CA (All Campuses), 09/03/2003-08/13/2004; O 8.43 (Box 9, Folder 215)
  - University of Michigan, 10/23/2001-04/06/2004; O 8.45 (Box 9, Folder 216)
  - University of Oregon, 10/14/1999-03/22/2004; O 8.47 (Box 9, Folder 217)
  - University of Southern California, 01/25/2000-06/22/2004; O 8.49 (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Western Association of Schools and Colleges (WASC), 11/14/2002-04/09/2004; O 8.52 (Box 9, Folder 219)
  - Yale University, 01/16/2002-05/25/2004; O 8.53 (Box 9, Folder 220)
  - Other Inaugurations, 02/18/2003-08/24/2004; O 8.55 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 06/30/2003-08/23/2004; O 11 (Box 9, Folder 222)
  - California Council on Science and Technology, 09/06/2002-10/02/2003; O 12 (Box 9, Folder 223)
  - American Philosophical Society, 06/02/2003-06/30/2004; O 15 (Box 9, Folder 224)
  - Research Misc., 07/10/2002-06/03/2004; R 0 (Box 9, Folder 225)
  - Sponsored Projects, 02/09/20001; R 1 (Box 9, Folder 226)
  - Women & Gender, 3/18/2004; R 1.8 (Box 9, Folder 227)
  - Institute for International Studies (IIS), 1/8/2004; R 1.12 (Box 9, Folder 228)
  - The Science Coalition, 12/11/2000-12/31/2003; R 8 (Box 9, Folder 229)
  - Student, Misc, 09/04/2003-08/31/2004; ST 1 (Box 9, Folder 230)
  - Student (Groups), 09/03/2003-01/05/2004; ST 1.1 (Box 9, Folder 231)
  - Ram's Head and Gaieties, 10/15/1999-12/04/2001; ST 1.3 (Box 9, Folder 232)
  - ASSU, 11/08/2002-04/20/2004; ST 2 (Box 9, Folder 233)
  - Bechtel International Center, 12/29/2002-08/06/2004; ST 3.5 (Box 9, Folder 234)
  - Student Radio, KZSU, 11/16/1999-06/04/2004; ST 3.18 (Box 9, Folder 235)
  - Haas Center, 06/12/2000-08/04/2003; ST 3.29 (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - Campus Compact, 09/13/1999-07/26/2004; ST 3.35 (Box 9, Folder 237)
  - Parent/Student Correspondence, 12/20/2002-06/09/2004; ST 8 (Box 9, Folder 238)
  - The Science Coalition, 12/11/2000-12/31/2003; R 8 (Box 9, Folder 239)
  - Students, Misc, 09/04/2003-08/31/2004; ST 1 (Box 9, Folder 240)
  - Student (Groups), 09/03/2003-01/05/2004; ST 1.1 (Box 9, Folder 241)
  - Ram's Head and Gaieties, 10/15/1999-12/04/2001; ST 1.3 (Box 9, Folder 242)
  - ASSU, 11/08/2002-04/20/2004; ST 2 (Box 9, Folder 243)
  - Bechtel International Center, 12/29/2002-08/06/2004; ST 3.5 (Box 9, Folder 244)
  - Student Radio, KZSU, 11/16/1999-06/04/2004; ST 3.18 (Box 9, Folder 245)
  - Haas Center, 06/12/2000-08/04/2003; ST 3.29 (Box 9, Folder 246)
  - Campus Compact, 09/13/1999-07/26/2004; ST 3.35 (Box 9, Folder 247)
  - Parent/Student Correspondence, 12/20/2002-06/09/2004; ST 8 (Box 9, Folder 248)
- President's records, 2004-2005; Accession ARCH-2007-164
  - Provost's Office, 09/02/2004-04/20/2005; AA 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dean of Chapel, 09/14/2004-05/03/2005; AA 1.8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Graduate Fellowships, 01/19/2005-03/17/2005; AA 1.12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Student Issues, 05/21/2002-07/27/2005; AA 1.13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Emeriti, 08/04/2005-08/05/2005; AA 2.2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Development (1 of 2), 01/24/2005-05/01/2005; AA 2.7 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Development (2 of 2), 05/17/2005; AA 2.7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - University Fellows, 04/01/2005-04/04/2005; AA 2.9 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Teaching & Research Assistant, 10/08/2004; AA 2.11 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Education/Issues, 02/09/2004-08/17/2005; AA 3 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Accreditation Issues / Very General/ CHEA, 08/27/2001-06/17/2005; AA 3.4 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - School of Humanities & Sciences, 09/01/2004-08/29/2005; AA 4.1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Humanities Center, 10/11/2004-03/30/2005; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Applied Physics, Dept of, 09/20/2004-10/13/2004; AA 4.1.8 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Art, Dept of (Academic), 10/20/2004-06/13/2005; AA 4.1.9 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chemistry, Dept of, 09/15/2004-05/11/2005; AA 4.1.13 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Computer Science, Dept of, 09/28/2004-08/08/2005; AA 4.1.17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Drama, Dept of, 09/10/2004-07/01/2005; AA 4.1.18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Economics, Dept of, 09/17/2004-05/02/2005; AA 4.1.20 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Inst. for Economic Policy Research (SIEPR), 09/15/2004-07/13/2005; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - English, Dept of, 11/03/2004-08/12/2005; AA 4.1.21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Department of French and Italian/Gumbrecht, Hans Ulrich, 02/16/2005-05/02/2005; AA 4.1.22 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - History, Dept of, 09/30/2004-03/08/2005; AA 4.1.25 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Hopkins Marine Station, 10/06/2004; AA 4.1.28 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Music, Dept of, 09/21/2004-07/19/2005; AA 4.1.29 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Athletics, Dept of, 06/15/2004-06/22/2005; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Football Games, 10/04/2004; AA 4.1.30/1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Physics, Dept of, 09/23/2004-08/24/2005; AA 4.1.33 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Political Science, Dept of, 09/20/2004; AA 4.1.34 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Psychology, Dept of, 12/30/2004-05/17/2005; AA 4.1.35 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Graduate School of Business, 09/07/2004-08/30/2005; AA 4.2 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Earth Science, School of, 09/28/2004-07/21/2005; AA 4.3 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Global Climate and Energy Project, GCEP, 09/07/2004; AA 4.3.1 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Engineering, School of, 08/02/2004-08/20/2005; AA 4.4 (Box 1, Folder 34)